<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Confessions of a Programmer</title><link>https://ioannakatsanou.github.io/Blog/</link><description>Recent content on Confessions of a Programmer</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ioannakatsanou.github.io/Blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Welcome Post</title><link>https://ioannakatsanou.github.io/Blog/post/welcome/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ioannakatsanou.github.io/Blog/post/welcome/</guid><description>I created this Blog a few months ago, with so many ideas and yet when the website was up and running, I did not bother to create even one blog post. So here is the first post. After working for about 7 years in a Large Corporate Tech company, I have many things to share, either code-oriented, or people oriented? If you also work at a tech company and live the programmer life, then you will know what I mean.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://ioannakatsanou.github.io/Blog/about/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ioannakatsanou.github.io/Blog/about/</guid><description>For the past 6 years I have been working as a programmer.
During that time I have gone through many programming work-related stages and have witnessed some incredible episodes at the work environment.
You might know what I am talking about if you are also a programmer otherwise you might need to stretch your imagination.
Ι decided to write this blog in order to share my adventures with you.
These may be accurate, or may have a dose of imagination – It is up to the reader to decide.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://ioannakatsanou.github.io/Blog/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ioannakatsanou.github.io/Blog/contact/</guid><description> To contact, please fill out the form below. Feel free to contant for any matter! Always interested to discuss, exchange point of views, all opinions are welcome!</description></item></channel></rss>